剧情回顾...
-站住 我会开枪的  -你不会 Sun
-Stop! Or I'll shoot!  -No, you won't Sun.
Jack  我需要你的帮助
Jack, I need your help.
这些不是她的
They're not hers.
她死了
She's gone.
这架飞机装满了海洛因
The plane was loaded with heroin.
你在哪里找到的?
Where did you find this?
-丛林里 我在丛林里找到的  -带我去
-In the jungle.I found it in the jungle.  -Take me there.
Eko 他是谁?
Eko? Who's that?
他是我兄弟
He's my brother.
原谅我 原谅我
Forgive me. Forgive me.
吃吧
Here, eat.
不会有事的 Yemi
It's okay, Yemi.
Eko
好了 去吧 Eko
All right, Eko. Go.
你没听到吗? 快去
Did you hear me? Go.
为你的偷窃忏悔
Confess that you have stolen.
Yemi当时很饿
Yemi was hungry.
这不是理由
That is not an excuse.
你有罪 Eko
You have sinned, Eko.
饿也不能偷东西
Hunger does not matter.
去吧 去请求上帝原谅
Now go.Ask God for forgiveness.
忏悔
Confess!
他像这样多久了?
How long has he been like this?
有几天了
Couple days, now.
Eko 听得到我说话吗?
Eko, can you hear me?
他发生了什么事?
What happened to him?
在我们从北极熊洞穴 救他之前还是之后?
Before or after we saved him from the polar bear cave?
走吧 Locke想确认你们都回来了
Come on. Locke will want to know you guys are back.
坚持下去老兄
Stay alive, dude.
好吗?
Okay?
你来这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我来忏悔
I have come to give my confession.
你好 Eko
Hello, Eko.
你好 兄弟
Hello, brother.
我有些货
I have some merchandise
-需要运到国外去  -毒品
-that I need to get out of the country.  -You mean drugs.
你把我们打扮成牧师 我们自己把货运出去
You make us priests and we will fly the drugs out ourselves.
即使我签了名 你们也不是牧师
My signature does not make you a priest, Eko.
你永远都不会成为牧师
You could never be a priest.
-别开枪 停下来  -Yemi
-No more! Stop now!  -Yemi
Yemi  不
神父
Father.
你还好吗 神父
Are you okay, father?
Eko 醒醒
Eko, wake up.
该做忏悔了...
It is time to confess...
你会被审判 兄弟
to be judged, brother.
我会等你的
I will be waiting.
你知道在哪里可以找到我
You know where to find me.
你们闻到烟味了吗?
You guys smell smoke?
把他拖出来
Get him clear!
帮帮我
Help me!
快 把他拖出来
Bring him out. Bring him out.
-我们得离开这里  -把他拖出来  快点
-We gotta get outta here.
用这个盖住他 小心点
Cover him with this. Be careful!
小心点
Be careful!
把他放下来  把他放下来
Lay him down.
没事了
You're okay.
你不会有事的
You're all right.
我的兄弟...
My brother...
我的....兄弟
My... brother.
你没事的  没事的
You're all right.It's okay. Okay.
你没事
You're all right.
我会回来的
I'll be back.
兄弟.... Yemi... .Yemi...
Brother... Yemi...
Charlie  大家都没事吗?
Charlie! Is everyone okay?
对  我们很好
Yeah. We're good.
Eko到哪里去了?
Where's Eko?
Hurley和我把他放在...
Hurley and I pulled him out over...
他刚刚还在这里
he was right there.
Eko?
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译： singa 后期：梁良 双语字幕：七色九天
晚上好  Jack
Good evening, Jack.
晚上好  Ben
Good evening, Ben.
我希望你愿意和我一起散步
I was hoping you might join me for a walk.
你的意思是
What?
如果我说不你也不会 在我头上带上袋子
Well,you say that like you're not gonna just throw a bag over my head
然后拖我出去吗
and drag me outta here if I say no.
那就别说不
Then don't say no.
把这个穿上好吗?
Why don't you put this on?
我在外面等
I'll wait outside.
会痛吗?
Does it hurt?
什么?
Sorry?
你的脖子 会痛吗?
Your neck, does it hurt?
会不会感到手指和脚趾麻木
Any numbness in your fingers and toes,
脚好像睡着了一般
like pins and needles when your foot falls asleep,
经常的?
but permanent?
你为什么问我这些问题  Jack?
Why are you asking me these questions, Jack?
因为  Ben  你脊柱附近有个肿瘤
Because, Ben,you have a tumor on your spine
一个迅速蔓延的肿瘤... 它会要了你的命
an aggressive tumor...that is going to kill you.
我不知道我看的那张X光片是什么时候照的
I don't know when those X-rays were taken that I saw,
除非那是最近才照的
but unless they were very recent
不然你以后都不能散步了
you're not gonna be taking walks much longer.
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
好吧  那我道歉
Okay. My mistake, then.
我准备好了
I'm ready whenever you are.
别走了
Stay here.
在我们送Colleen上路之前
As we prepare to send Colleen on her way,
我想占用点时间...
I'd like to take a moment...
我讨厌葬礼
I hate funerals.
他让你出来了?
He let you out?
还给了我一件新衣服
Gave me a new shirt, too.
再见  Jack
Bye, Jack.
你为什么给他看我的X光片?
Why did you show him my X-rays?
我没告诉他那是你的
I didn't tell him they were yours.
但我猜他知道了
But I guess you did.
我想我知道该怎么找Jack  Kate和Sawyer了
I think I know how to find Jack, Kate and Sawyer.
我能问问为什么 他也被邀请来谈话了吗?
Can I ask why he's being included in the conversation?
是为了伤害我的感情吗?
Is that supposed to hurt my feelings?
把你告诉我的告诉他
Tell him what you told me.
舱门下面的电脑
The computer in the hatch
不只是用来按按钮
wasn't only for pushing the button.
我相信它可以用来
I'm pretty sure
和其他站交流
that it can be used to communicate with other stations.
这太棒了 不过你刚才不是说舱门下面被炸了吗
This is fascinating,but you just told me the hatch exploded.
只有其中一个
One of them did.
你想试着和其他站联系
You want to try and communicate with the others.
对
Yep.
不好了老兄
No luck, dudes.
我们都找遍了  Eko不见了
We looked everywhere.Eko's gone.
没有发现痕迹
There was no trail.
没有我们能识别的痕迹
Not that we, like, know what a trail looks like.
你们把他从帐篷拖出来的时候 他说了什么吗?
When you pulled him out of the tent, did he say anything?
断断续续的
Nothing coherent.
他迷迷糊糊的说 "我的兄弟 我的兄弟"
He was just mumbling "my brother, my brother."
Sayid  带上你的装备 我们去找那个电脑
Sayid, pack your gear.We're going to that computer.
等一下  Eko怎么办?
Wait. What about Eko?
我们能追上他
We'll catch up to him.
我们要去的是同一个地方
We're all going to the same place.
你到家了  神父
You're home, father.
神父?
Father?
我在找Yemi
I was looking for father Yemi.
Yemi神父他...离开了
Father Yemi is... Is gone.
他突然被叫走了...
He was called away quite suddenly...
南方的难民露营地出了紧急事故
an emergency at the refugee camp down south.
我是Amina  我在诊所工作
I am Amina.I work at the clinic.
这是我儿子Daniel
This is my son Daniel.
他在这里当祭坛男孩
He's the altar boy here.
你替他的班?
Are you taking his place?
是
Yes.
Yemi神父还会去伦敦吗?
Will father Yemi still go to London?
伦敦?
London?
他计划这个周末就出发
He was leaving at the end of the week.
他去完成学业
He was going to continue his studies.
我会替他去
I will take his place there, too.
不  别
Don't! No!
求你了
Please!
不!
忏悔
Confess.
我们要去的珍珠站 有台电脑可能会帮助我们找到我们的人
We're headed now to the Pearl station.There's a
computer there that might help us find our people.
有人愿意和我们一起去吗?
Anybody want to come along?
你说"有人愿意和我们一起去吗"是什么意思?
What do you mean:"Anybody wanna come along"?
我的意思是 想来就来 岛上的景点都是免费的
I mean, if you'd like to join us,it's a free island.
没错  但是Jack都是一个人做事情
Yeah, see, Jack would go and do stuff alone
或者他带上Sayid或者Kate
or he'd take Sayid or Kate.
是的  没错  但我不是Jack
Yeah, well, I'm not Jack.
人多力量大
The more the merrier.
-我去  -很好
-I'll go.  -Great.
什么?
What?
其他想来的人十分钟以后在树那里集合
Anybody else wanna come, meet us at the tree line in ten minutes.
带上水
Bring water.
你不是认真的吧
You're not serious.
你不是总抱怨他们不带上我们吗?
What? You always whine about not being included.
现在机会来了
Now's our chance.
你介意我问你一些问题吗  兄弟?
Do you mind if I ask you a question, brother?
说
Shoot.
我们是去找电脑
Are we going off to poke at a computer,
还是去找你们的Eko?
or are we going after your man Eko?
一箭双雕
Two birds, one stone.
Eko去了飞机坠毁的地方
Eko's heading for the plane that crashed
就在舱门的上面
on top of the entrance to the Pearl station.
是吗  太巧了
Well, that's quite a coincidence.
不要把命运和巧合搞混了
Don't mistake coincidence for fate.
你不该那样做
You're not supposed to do that.
那是圣水
That's holy water.
我用它洗去罪恶
I'm washing away my sins.
Yemi神父从来不...
Father Yemi would never...
我不是Yemi神父
I'm not father Yemi.
别动
Wait there!
Yemi神父在哪里?
Where... Where is father Yemi?
谁想知道?
Who wants to know?
也许你没听清楚
Perhaps you did not hear me.
我说  Yemi神父在哪里?
I said,where is father Yemi?
货还没到  我刚接到电话
The shipment is late.I just got off the telephone.
他们保证星期五会到的
They assure me it will arrive on Friday.
什么货?
What shipment?
你应该告诉你们的新神父我们之间的协议
You should explain our arrangement to your new priest.
收到的红十字会疫苗中...
We receive shipments of vaccines from the Red Cross.
我们保留20%
We are allowed to keep 20%.
剩下的给Emeka和他的人
The rest, we give to Emeka and his men.
这是保护费
In exchange for protection.
那么...你看  神父
So you see, father...
大家都很高兴吧
everybody is happy, huh?
大家都很高兴
Everybody's happy.
大家都得到了好处
Everybody benefits.
所以我希望你继续我们的协议
So I hope you will continue to honor our arrangement.
我不怕你
I am not afraid of you.
我星期五来取疫苗  神父
I'll be back for the vaccine on Friday, father.
你不想再死人了吧
You don't want more lives on your conscience.
你好  Eko
猜猜午餐吃什么?
You wanna guess what's for lunch?
我不擅长猜谜
I'm not...I'm not big on mysteries.
当然
Of course you're not.
你们有干酪汉堡?
You people have cheeseburgers?
你不知道
You have no idea
为了做这个给你我费了多少心
what I went through to make this for you.
我杀了牛  割下肉
I killed the cow,processed the meat,
烘烤芝麻
baked the bun.
还有面包...
And the fries...
用动物油炸的
try rendering animal fat.
没有调味番茄酱吗?
No ketchup?
-我想和他谈谈  -好 谈吧
-I'd like to talk to him.  -Okay, so talk to him.
可以单独谈吗
Alone, please.
我不介意她听
I'm fine with her being here.
我知道你不介意  Jack
And I'm thrilled that you're fine, Jack,
但这是隐私
but it's private.
医生和病人之间的秘密?
Doctor-patient confidentiality?
当然  没问题
Sure.Of course.
介意我吃东西吗?
Mind if I eat?
我们有一个很好的击败你的计划  Jack
We had such a wonderful plan to break you, Jack.
击败我?
Break me?
骗过你
Wear you down
等到你相信我们不是你的敌人
until you were convinced we weren't your enemies.
得到你的信任
Get you to trust us.
到时候  我们让你相信
And then, of course,we'd lead you to believe
你做的事都是上天安排的
that you were choosing to do whatever we asked you to do.
当然这都是计划  你自己会思考
All of this assumed, of course,that you would get invested.
思考什么?
Invested in what?
你发现了吗?
Has it not occurred to you
Juliet和你的前妻很像
that Juliet bears a striking resemblance to your ex-wife?
为什么给我说这些?
Why are you telling me this?
这是因为  Jack
I'm telling you this, Jack,
我完美的计划曝光了
because my wonderful plan got shot to sunshine
当你看到我的X光片发现我快死了的时候
when you saw my damned X-rays and figured out I was dying.
这一切...
All of this...
你为了让我给你动手术把我带到这里
you brought me here to operate on you.
你...
You...
你想我救你的命
you want me to save your life.
不 我让你想要救我的命
No, I want you to want to save my life.
但现在已经不行了
But we're beyond that now, so...
我想说的就是你能否考虑一下
all I can ask is that you think about it.
你相信上帝吗  Jack?
Do you believe in God, Jack?
你呢?
Do you?
两天前我发现
Two days after I found out
我脊柱附近有个致命的肿瘤之后
I had a fatal tumor on my spine,
突然出现了一个外科医生
a spinal surgeon fell out of the sky.
如果这不是有上帝的证据
And if that's not proof of God,
那是什么
I don't know what is.
你真的没事吗?
You sure you're all right?
我们可以停下来喘口气
We can stop for a bit and catch our breaths.
我没事
I'm fine.
你要去飞机坠毁的地方  是吗?
You're heading for the plane wreckage, aren't you?
Charlie听到你在叫你的兄弟
Charlie heard you call out for your brother
在你离开帐篷之前
before you left the camp.
那就是你来这里的原因吗?
Is that what you're doing out here,
找Yemi?
looking for Yemi?
不要再说我兄弟的名字
Do not speak my brother's name again.
你怎么这么害怕  Eko?
What are you so afraid of, Eko?
两天之内再回来检查一下
You need to come back in two days.
神父
Father.
我能为你做什么?
What can I do for you?
那就是你说的疫苗吗
It's that the vaccines that you spoke of...
货什么时候到一次?
how often do the shipments come?
六个月一次  如果我们运气好的话
Every six months,if we are lucky.
你怎么对我们的
What makes you so interested
疫苗这么感兴趣?
in our shipments of vaccine, father?
你同意把大部分都给土匪?
You agreed to give most of it to the militia?
疫苗在黑市上售价很高
The vaccines fetch a high price on the black market.
不管你在想什么 别惹那些人
Whatever you are thinking, do not cross these men.
Yemi神父来之前  我们什么都没有
Before father Yemi,we got nothing.
这些疫苗都是他的功劳
We owe whatever vaccines we have to his work.
你让我想起了他
You remind me of him,you know.
你也是个好人
You are a good man, too.
听说你想卖些疫苗
I hear you have some vaccine to sell.
对  但星期天之前必须成交
I do, but it has to be done by Sunday.
我要离开这个国家了
I'm leaving the country.
没问题
No problem.
舱门就在飞机下面
The hatch is over here by the plane.
你把大家带下去好吗?
Why don't you take everybody down?
你呢?
And you?
我暂时不下去
I'll be there in a minute.
Eko在找什么?
What's Eko looking for?
飞机里那具他兄弟的尸体
His brother's body's in that plane.
告诉我...
So...
你到底看到了什么?
what exactly did you see back there?
我也看到过
I saw it once, you know.
你看到了什么?
What did you see?
我看到一道很亮的光
I saw a very bright light.
它很美
It was beautiful.
我看到的不是那个
That is not what I saw.
我兄弟不见了
My brother's gone.
你把飞机烧了  Yime的尸体可能烧化了
You set the plane on fire.Yemi's body could have burned.
或者..或者是有动物...
Not to mention animals or...
那么...你想和我们一起下去吗?
so... you don't wanna come down there with us?
不  我在这里等你们
No, I will wait here.
好吧
Well...
差点忘记了
Oh, I forgot.
找你的时候我发现了这个
I found this when I was looking for you.
你好  神父
Hello, father.
我听说你有一批疫苗要卖
I hear you have a shipment of vaccine for sale.
如果你认为
If you thought
你可以背着我干这些事情
you could do this without me knowing,
那么你不了解我
you don't know who I am.
知道吗...
You know...
你很幸运  神父
you're lucky, father.
我是个迷信的人
I'm a superstitious man.
我不喜欢夺走神职人员的性命
I don't relish taking the life of a holy man.
所以今天
That is why, today,
我要砍了你的手
I'm only going to cut off your hands.
求你了  别这样
Please! No!
你不知道我是谁
You do not know who I am.
我是Mark Wickmund博士 这是...
I'm Dr.Mark Wickmund, and this is the orientation film
达摩启动计划第五站的介绍电影
for station five of Dharma Initiative.
第五站  或者说珍珠
Station five, or the Pearl,
是一个监视站
is a monitoring station
用来监视和记录
where the activities of participants
达摩计划参与者的活动...
in Dharma Initiative projects can be observed and recorded...
怎么样?
Well?
只有一根导线
The wiring is only one way.
这是个闭合系统  死胡同
It's a closed system,a dead end.
伙计们?
Hey, guys?
其他的影片讲的是什么?
What are these other TVs for?
什么?
Sorry?
所有的影片
All these TVs.
这个人说这里有六个站
This guy says that there's six stations.
就在这里  看吧
All right, here.Check it out.
...是一个监视站
...is a monitoring station
用来监视和记录
where the activities of the participants
达摩启动计划
in Dharma Initiative projects
参与者的活动...
can be observed and recorded...
"计划"不只一个
Projects. More than one.
所以这里的其他一些影片 可能和其他舱门有联系
So maybe some of these TVs are connected to the other hatches.
我突然觉得自己很笨
Well, I'm suddenly feeling very stupid.
也许我可以接上另一根线
Perhaps I could patch in one of the other feeds,
看看能不能得到其他影像
see if we can get another picture.
你们在珍珠的任务持续三个星期...
Your tour of duty in the Pearl will last three weeks...
厕所还是好的
The toilet still works.
有图像吗?
Anything yet?
没有
Nothing.
现在呢?
What about now?
-John?  -有图像了
-John?  -Yeah, we got something.
这是什么?
What is it?
这个问题提得不错
That's a good question.
这些是电脑
Those are computers.
太好了 这就是你们要找的东西
Great. That's what you're looking for.
现在我们可以离开这里了
Now we can get out of here.
我想他会期待我们的到访
I guess he'll be expecting us.
你不再相信我了吗?
You don't trust me anymore?
我相信你  我只是来放电影的
I trust you just fine.Just thought I'd put a movie in.
你知道吗  我很不想看电影
You know what? I'm gonna pass on the movie.
你会喜欢的 这是"杀掉一只知更鸟"
You'll like this one, Jack.It's "To kill a mockingbird."
-是部经典片  -我现在真的不想看
-It's a classic.  -I don't wanna watch a movie right now.
那我把声音关了吧
I'll turn the sound down, then.
我觉得我应该向你道歉
I felt like I should apologize,say I'm sorry.
我很抱歉带你来这里
I'm sorry for bringing you here
也对我们做的所有事情
and for everything that's been done to you
以及你的朋友道歉
and your friends.
但你必须知道...
But you have to know...
我们情非得以
we were desperate.
为了拯救他的生命我们只能这么做 (别管我在说什么)
It was also we could save his life.
Ben...
他是个很好的人
he's a great man.
我知道你很难相信 但是真的 (Ben是个骗子)
I know you find that hard to believe,but he is.
也许你会觉得...你没有选择 (而且他很危险)
You probably feel like...you don't have a choice,
其实不是的  Jack
but you do, Jack.
大家都有自由选择的权力对吗? (我们想要反抗他  但必须让别人以为是事故)
Free will is all we've really got, right?
无论如何...
Anyway...
只是想告诉你我的想法 (看起来我们好像要救他  剩下的就靠你了)
just wanted to put in my two cents.
我以前告诉过你你可以相信我
I told you before you can trust me.
现在我希望你能相信我
I want you to trust me now,
我希望你做外科手术
when I tell you that doing the surgery is
对你来说这是件好事 (这是个很复杂的外科手术  其他人不会知道)
absolutely the right thing for you to do.
因为他应该活下去 (我会保护你的)
It's the right thing,because he deserves  to live.
(现在叫我把电影关了)
关掉电影
Turn the movie off.
Jack...
关了  马上
Turn it off. Now.
好的  关了
All right. It's off.
请你考虑一下我的建议
Think about what I said...please.
你去哪里?
Where are you going?
伦敦
London.
你是坏人吗?
Are you a bad man?
妈妈说你是个坏人
My mom says you are a bad man.
上帝才知道
Only God knows.
你拿到疫苗了
I see you have your vaccine.
你想我感谢你吗?
Do you expect me to be grateful?
我知道你想干什么
I know what you were planning to do.
那些人  我帮助他们...
Those men, I helped...
会有其他人代替他们的
Those men will be replaced by other men.
他们在干什么? 他们这是什么意思?
What are they doing?What is the meaning of this?
他们正在封教堂
They are boarding up the church.
我们不能再用它了
We can no longer use it.
这是Yemi的教堂 你们没有权力这么做
This is Yemi's church.You have no right to do this.
它已经不神圣了
It is no longer sacred,
有一天你因为你做的事遭到报应的
and one day, you'll be judged for what you did.
如果我是你
If I were you,
我会开始过安宁的生活
I would start making my peace now.
我会去伦敦然后开始反悔
I would go to London and begin to repent,
因为你欠了上帝你带走的那几条人命
because you owe God for every life you've taken.
你真的觉得这是Yemi的吗?
And you truly believe this is Yemi's?
你还欠了他一座教堂
You owe him one church.
Yemi
等一下
Wait.
Yemi
你说过你想听我忏悔
You say you want to hear my confession.
为什么? 为什么是现在?
Why? Why now, eh?
快出来
Show yourself!
你在哪里?
Where are you?
哪里?
Where?
准备好了吗  Eko?
Are you ready, Eko?
是的
Yes.
我准备好了  Yemi
I am ready, Yemi.
我不希望得到原谅  神父...
I ask for no forgiveness,father...
因为我没有罪
for I have not sinned.
我只是做了为了活下来所必须做的事
I have only done what I needed to do to survive.
一个小男孩曾经问我
A small boy once asked me
我是不是坏人
if I was a bad man.
如果我现在可以回答他
If I could answer him now,
我会告诉他
I would tell him
我还是个小男孩的时候
that when I was a young boy,
为了救我的兄弟我杀了一个人
I killed a man to save my brother's life.
我不为这感到抱歉
I am not sorry for this.
我为此感到自豪
I am proud of this.
我没有要求得到上帝给我的生命
I did not ask for the life that I was given,
虽然如此我还是得到生命了
but it was given nonetheless.
我尽力生活
I did my best.
你对我说话就像对你兄弟一样
You speak to me as if I were your brother.
你是谁?
Who are you?
上帝是我的引导者  我不会...
The Lord is my shepherd.I shall not want...
Eko?
天哪  Eko
没事了  没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
他说什么? John
What did he say, John?
接下来就轮到我们了
He said...we're next.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■